Larissa Furlan Branco

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented professional with top skills in customer relations, problem-solving and recordkeeping. Talented in addressing different service and product problems with thorough and positive style. Ready to help with focus on finding creative solutions to conflicts and complaints. +5 years of experience in backoffice and administrative routines.

EXPERIENCE

Concentrix - Customer Service Advisor

Dublin, Ireland 05/2022 - Current

- Listened to individual complaints with open mind and asked detailed questions to understand issues.
- Coordinated referrals and escalations to obtain specialised support.
- Completed Salesforce documentation and associated forms for new actions.
- Stayed current on policies, procedures and standards to offer optimal support.
- Processed refunds, exchanges and service requests for customers.

The Strand Gastro Pubs Ltd. - Customer Service Representative Dublin, Ireland 10/2019 - 05/2022

- Facilitated excellent customer experience by providing friendly, attentive and proactive customer service.
- Suggested products to customers based on dietary requests and latest food trends.
- Maintained outstanding customer satisfaction by delivering food and drinks on time in high-pressure environments.
- Monitored inventory levels, promptly ordering low-stocked supplies and ordering extra for busier periods.
- Took orders, using effective upselling techniques to increase customer interest in additional products.

Weston Facilities Services Ltd. - Front Desk Receptionist

Dublin, Ireland

04/2019 - 10/2019

- Delivered polite, professional customer service to enhance business reputation through positive first impressions.
- Welcomed guests and clients in friendly, positive manner.
- Maintained clean and orderly reception area to impress and welcome visitors.

54, Dorset Street Upper - Dublin ,D01VX09 +353 83 387 9271 larissa.furlanbranco@outlook.com

SKILLS

- · Account management
- After-sales support
- Telephone switchboard operation
- · Refund and exchange
- Salesforce CRM
- SAP CRM
- · Order processing
- Data entry
- Administrative skills
- Microsoft Office proficiency
- Multitasking ability
- Meticulous eye for detail
- Supplier relations
- Inventory coordination
- Strong interpersonal skills
- Administrative operations
- Improving procedures
- File maintenance
- Back office operations

EDUCATION

2013

E.E. Professor Silvio José Secco Jacareí, Brazil

High School Diploma

CERTIFICATIONS

- Advanced Excel certified
- Electrician certified

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• Driving license: A and B

- Answered and directed incoming calls to relevant staff members using multi-line telephone system.
- Processed and distributed incoming correspondence to relevant staff, facilitating team communication.

Capua Projetos e Construções LTDA - Assistant Buyer

Jacareí , Brazil 02/2015 - 11/2018

- Negotiated supplier contract and terms, including SLAs, price, lead time, delivery terms and returns.
- Investigated and resolved supply chain issues through collaboration with Inventory team.
- Provided technical product support for commercial and sales teams on new business tenders.
- Worked with shipment companies to manage distribution.
- Managed purchases, receipts and the documentation of finished goods, materials, packaging and ingredients.
- Expeditiously and effectively resolved purchasing claim issues.
- Progressed through various purchasing, warehousing and leadership roles.
- Developed and managed cost reduction and waste elimination policies.

Capua Projetos e Construções LTDA - Administrative Assistant

Jacareí , Brazil 07/2012 - 02/2015

- Answered phones and performed clerical office functions.
- Handled client correspondence and internal communications in professional manner.
- Organised and stored hardcopy files.
- Performed administrative tasks, document management and report development for inter-departmental use.
- Helped less experienced staff manage daily assignments.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: First Language

English: C2

Proficient